♪No matter how far the distance is, don’t be afraid♪
♪아무리 떨어져 있어도 두려워하지 마세요♪
♪Love is gentle and caring♪
♪사랑은 부드럽고 걱정으로 가득 차 있습니다♪
♪Those scars will always heal♪
♪그 상처는 언제나 아물 거야♪
♪They will come together like the flowers of time♪
♪그들은 시간의 꽃처럼 모일 것이다♪
♪Someone will eventually collect them for you♪
♪그리고 결국 누군가가 당신을 위해 그것들을 수집할 것입니다♪
♪Keep going, you won’t be alone♪
♪계속 가세요. 당신은 혼자가 아닐 거예요♪
♪Conversation with time♪
♪시간과 대화하세요♪
♪When the light falls softly, think of it as the answer♪
♪빛이 은은하게 내리면 대답으로 받아들이세요♪
♪May you find someone in the vast sea of ​​people♪
♪ 그 넓은 사람의 바다에서 누군가를 찾길 ♪
♪Take a cup of tea and be happy♪
♪가벼운 차를 즐기며 행복해요♪
♪Understand that life is full of regrets♪
♪인생은 후회로 가득 차 있다는 것을 이해 ♪
♪There is still love♪
♪그래도 사랑해요♪
♪Winter and summer♪
♪겨울과 여름♪
【Love is a panacea】 【Episode 7】
[사랑은 만병통치약] [7화]
[Works funded by major art projects in Sichuan Province in 2022]
[ 2022년 쓰촨성 주요 예술 프로젝트 지원 작품 ]
[Adapted from Meng Yuyan’s novel "Healing"]
[레몬 위얀의 소설 '힐링'을 각색함 ]
If there's nothing more to say, I'll leave first.
더 할말 없으면 나 먼저 갈게.
I need to go to the embassy to apply for an emergency visa.
긴급 비자를 처리하기 위해 대사관에 가야 합니다 .
According to our contract,
우리 계약에 따르면,
Resignation must be submitted one week in advance.
사직은 일주일 전에 요청해야 합니다.
The resignation will be effective one week after submission.
사직서는 제출 후 일주일 후에 발효됩니다 .
During this time,
이 기간 동안,
You have to keep working.
계속 일해야 해요.
if you are missing,
누락된 경우,
They will deduct your wages.
그들은 당신의 급여를 공제할 것입니다.
no problem.
괜찮아요.
Until this Sunday, right?
이번주 일요일까지죠?
Don't worry. I will work until the last day.
마지막 날까지 일하겠습니다.
And even if I leave,
그리고 내가 떠나더라도,
Jiang Muying can replace me.
Jiang Muying이 내 자리를 대신할 수 있습니다.
Please remember to pay me my salary.
나에게 월급을 지불하는 것을 잊지 마십시오.
[resignation letter]
[사직서]
Wei'an.
웨이안.
I'm looking for you.
나는 당신을 찾고 있어요.
my boss wants
내 상사가 원해
You translate it all for him.
당신이 그를 위해 이 모든 것을 번역해 준 것입니다.
If you don't complete the translation, you won't be able to leave.
번역을 마치지 않으면 나갈 수 없습니다.
He said that instead of helping others solve their problems, teach them.
그는 다른 사람들이 문제를 해결하도록 돕는 것보다 가르치는 것이 더 낫다고 말했습니다.
It seems to me that he doesn't want you to leave.
내 생각엔 그 사람은 당신이 떠나는 걸 원하지 않는 것 같아요.
What are you two doing?
둘이 무슨 일이에요?
they are.
그들은.
has a problem. Sakun's condition worsened and he was hospitalized again.
뭔가 잘못되었다. 사쿤의 상태는 더욱 악화돼 ​​다시 병원에 입원했다.
He is looking for you everywhere.
그는 어디에서나 당신을 찾고 있습니다.
Saquon.
사쿤.
Where does it hurt?
어디가 아프니?
It hurts everywhere.
어디든 아프다.
pain?
통증?
Where does it hurt?
어디가 아프니?
It hurts everywhere.
어디든 아프다.
let me see.
어디 보자.
Wei'an's mother, don't leave.
엄마 웨이안, 가지 마세요.
It would be nice if that was possible.
그렇게 될 수 있다면 정말 좋을 것 같아요.
Saquon.
사쿤.
It seems that the toxin has spread throughout the body.
독소가 몸 전체로 퍼진 것 같습니다 .
TCM acupuncture is necessary
한의학이 필요하다
Delete it.
삭제하려면.
Do you know what TCM acupuncture is?
중국 침술이 무엇인지 아시나요?
This is a long needle
긴 바늘이에요
insert into your body,
몸에 삽입되는 것,
But it doesn't hurt at all.
하지만 전혀 아프지 않아요.
Wei'an's mother, I don't feel pain anywhere.
엄마 웨이안님, 이제 아무데도 안 아파요.
Saquon.
사쿤.
I have an incurable disease
고칠 수 없는 병이 있는데 ,
like you.
너 같이.
but now
그러나 지금
they found a cure
그들은 치료법을 발견했습니다
for this disease.
이 질병에 대해.
So I have to go to France.
그래서 프랑스로 가야 해요.
This is my last chance
내 마지막 기회야.
Wei'an's mother, don't leave.
엄마 웨이안, 가지 마세요.
Don't worry.
괜찮아요.
I will come back to see you as soon as possible
최대한 빨리 돌아와서 뵙겠습니다.
OK?
좋아요?
Mama Vianne.
엄마 웨이안.
Come on, go to bed first.
자, 먼저 자러 가세요.
Jiang.
장.
Don't do this again.
더 이상 그러지 마세요.
I will definitely go to France.
나는 꼭 프랑스에 갈 것이다.
If Saquon gets sick again
사쿤이 또 아프면
Please take good care of him.
그를 잘 돌봐주세요.
Vian, Saquon needs you very much.
웨이안, 사쿤은 당신이 매우 필요합니다.
Friendship Hospital needs you too.
우정병원 에도 당신이 필요합니다.
And Dr. Gu and I,
그리고 나와 구 박사님,
We all need you.
우리 모두는 당신이 필요합니다.
Don't leave, okay?
가지 마세요, 알았죠?
Right, Dr. Gu?
그렇죠, 구 박사님?
Doctor Gu.
구 박사님.
They will find a better translator soon.
그들은 곧 더 나은 번역가를 찾을 것입니다 .
Without me, Friendship Hospital would not be necessary.
나 없이는 우정병원이 꼭 필요하지 않다.
No.
아니요.
As...?
처럼...?
you're right.
네가 옳아.
No matter who is here or not, the Earth will continue to spin.
지구는 누가 있든 없든 계속 회전할 것입니다.
What does Friendship Hospital need?
우정병원에 필요한 것
Not just translation skills,
번역 실력뿐만 아니라
And it also has long-term stability.
장기적인 안정성도 있습니다.
we don't need translators
우리는 번역가가 필요하지 않습니다
Let them come and go as they please.
그들이 원하는 대로 오고 가도록 놔두세요.
I told you,
내가 전에 말했잖아,
You are not the right person.
당신은 옳은 사람이 아닙니다.
【Friendship Hospital】
[우정병원]
Yunzheng, I'm sorry.
윤정 씨, 미안해요.
I really want to spend your birthday with you .
나는 정말로 당신의 생일에 당신과 함께 있고 싶습니다 .
But I still have work to do.
하지만 보류 중인 작업이 있습니다.
liar.
거짓말쟁이.
Mom, you are a big liar.
엄마, 당신은 대단한 거짓말쟁이예요.
(Yunzheng, prometo)
(윤정, 프로메토)
(I'll get back to you soon.)
(곧 당신 곁으로 돌아갈게요.)
(I promise.)
(약속해요.)
(You said the same thing last time.)
(지난번에도 그렇게 말씀하셨어요.)
(I don’t believe you anymore.)
(나는 더 이상 당신을 믿지 않습니다.)
(You are a bad mother.)
(당신은 나쁜 엄마예요.)
(Better not come back.)
(돌아오지 않는 것이 좋습니다.)
(You are not the mother I want.)
(당신은 내가 원하는 엄마가 아니다.)
grandfather.
할아버지.
Yunzheng.
윤정.
Have you eaten yet?
식사하셨나요?
Are you busy lately?
요즘 바빠요?
All right.
괜찮은.
I'm not very busy.
나는 별로 바쁘지 않다.
It seems that you are not in a good mood.
기분이 좋지 않은 것 같습니다.
You can tell me what happened to you.
당신에게 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는지 말해 줄 수 있습니다.
grandfather.
할아버지.
I still don't understand
나는 결코 이해하지 못한다
Why do I want to keep these people?
왜 내가 유지하고 싶은 사람들인가?
of.
그 자체.
Yunzheng.
윤정.
listen to me.
내 말을 들어보세요.
for some things,
어떤 것에는
You shouldn't keep them to yourself.
절대로 혼자만 보관해서는 안 됩니다.
You have to talk about them so the other person understands.
상대방이 이해할 수 있도록 이야기해야 합니다 .
Don't live with lifelong regrets by keeping secrets.
비밀을 간직한 것에 대해 평생 후회 하지 마십시오 .
Just out of shame, you know?
부끄러워서요, 알겠어요?
[Jinhai City] Grandpa, what makes you so happy?
[진하이시] 할아버지, 무엇이 그리 기쁘신가요?
I just called Yunzheng.
방금 윤정에게 전화했어요.
perhaps
아마도
in love
사랑에 빠지다
In Lakaya?
라카야에서?
That is.
그건.
It seems
외모
Who worries...
누가 걱정해?
Scissors.
가위.
For something related to love.
사랑과 관련된 것.
In all these years, I've never heard anyone say that.
그렇게 오랜 세월이 흐른 뒤에도 나는 그런 사람의 말을 들어 본 적이 없습니다.
I didn't expect that his fate would be abroad.
그의 운명이 해외에 있을 것이라고 는 상상도 못했습니다 .
It would be great if you could bring your girlfriend to meet us.
우리가 만날 수 있도록 여자친구를 데려오실 수 있다면 정말 좋을 것 같아요.
Let's hope.
희망을 가지 자.
The girl Yunzheng likes
윤정이가 좋아했던 여자
It must be very good.
그것은 아주 좋은 것임에 틀림없다.
Why are you so thin?
왜 그렇게 말랐나요?
[Lakaya]
[라카야]
I’ll just call you Bian, okay?
난 비안이라고 부를게, 알았지?
Hey Bian.
안녕, 비안.
How can we get Wei An to stay?
웨이안(Wei'an)에 머물게 하려면 어떻게 해야 합니까?
She is determined to elope with Eliot.
그녀는 엘리엇과 함께 도망치기로 결심한다.
I've tried it but it doesn't work.
이미 시도했지만 작동하지 않습니다.
Do you have any ideas?
어떤 생각이 있나요?
Jiang.
장.
You ruined all my makeup.
당신이 내 화장을 다 망쳤어요.
You also put my lipstick on you.
심지어 내 립스틱도 너한테 발랐잖아.
I haven't blamed you yet.
나는 아직 당신을 비난하지 않았습니다.
If I just go back to the office wearing a white coat
이렇게 하얀 가운을 입고 회사에 돌아가면
my boss will think
내 상사가 생각할 거야
I'm dealing with love affairs.
연애 문제로 출장 중이에요 .
He won't think badly of you.
그는 당신을 나쁘게 생각하지 않을 것입니다.
He will only envy you.
그는 당신을 부러워할 것입니다.
I didn't expect my boss to be jealous of me.
상사가 나를 부러워할 거라고 는 상상도 못했어요 .
your boss
너의 상사
What a waste of my handsome face.
정말 잘생긴 얼굴을 낭비하고 있구나 .
He is stupid.
그는 매우 바보입니다.
He is completely immune to love.
그는 사랑에 완전히 면역되어 있습니다.
He even hoped that he could bring Wei An home.
그는 심지어 Wei'an을 집으로 데려올 수 있기를 바랐습니다.
I think too much.
나는 생각을 너무 많이 하고 있었다.
Su Weian fell in love with Elliot.
Su Wei'an은 Eliot를 사랑합니다.
What can my boss do?
우리 상사는 무엇을 할 수 있나요?
I don't think she wanted to run away with Elliot.
내 생각엔 그녀가 엘리엇과 함께 도망치고 싶어하는 것 같지는 않아요.
No one knows Vian better than me.
나보다 Wei'an을 더 잘 아는 사람은 없습니다.
She and Gu Yunzheng like each other.
그녀와 Gu Yunzheng은 서로 좋아합니다.
My radar couldn't be wrong.
내 레이더가 틀릴 리가 없어.
I have.
나는 그것을 가지고 있습니다.
I have a way to hold Su Wei'an.
나에겐 소웨이안을 붙잡을 방법이 있다.
【Friendship Hospital】
[우정병원]
It's already ten o'clock.
벌써 10시네요.
With the surgery we're going to do later,
수술은 나중에 하도록 할게요.
There will be five in total.
총 5개가 됩니다.
A new record.
새로운 기록.
boss.
사장.
Why don't you look tired at all?
전혀 피곤해 보이지 않는 이유는 무엇입니까?
I'm used to it.
나는 그것에 익숙해졌습니다.
This is real.
사실이에요.
Translator Su was present,
여기 번역가 Su와 함께,
No matter how many surgeries you undergo, you will never feel tired.
수술을 더 하셔도 피곤하지 않으실 거예요 .
Her time as a translator here is coming to an end.
번역가로서의 그녀의 시간이 이제 끝나가고 있습니다.
if you feel tired,
피곤함을 느끼면,
You do not need to attend your next surgery.
다음 수술에는 참여할 필요가 없습니다 .
You can let Jiang Muying take your place.
Jiang Muying이 당신을 대신하도록 할 수 있습니다.
It's not necessary
필요하지 않습니다.
Anyway, this is the last surgery.
어쨌든 이번이 마지막 수술이다.
Bueno.
부에노.
【Friendship Hospital】
[우정병원]
[Operation in progress]
[작업 진행 중]
boss.
사장.
This is the workbook for our medical team.
저희 의료진의 업무 매뉴얼입니다 .
Su Yi has translated it for you.
Su 번역가 가 이미 번역했습니다.
This is a task assigned to you,
이것은 당신이 직접 할당한 임무입니다.
So you should evaluate it yourself.
그러니 스스로 평가해야 한다.
I can't continue.
계속할 수 없습니다.
I need to go to sleep.
난 자러 가야 해.
You and translator Su
당신과 번역가 Su
You can review it bit by bit.
차근차근 복습하시면 됩니다.
leave.
떠나다.
Fang Mingfan.
팡밍판.
Be sure to check thoroughly.
철저하게 검토해 보시기 바랍니다.
I don't want to owe you anything.
나는 당신에게 아무것도 빚지고 싶지 않습니다.
So, we can't just stand here.
그러니 우리는 여기에 가만히 있을 수는 없습니다.
Let's go to the office.
사무실로 가자.
Are you sure this will work?
이것이 효과가 있다고 확신합니까?
Clear.
분명한.
Last time they spent the night together in the pharmacy,
지난번에는 약국에서 함께 하룻밤을 보냈는데 ,
Their relationship took a giant leap.
그리고 그들의 관계는 큰 도약을 이루었습니다.
Now we leave them alone in the room,
이제 우리는 그들을 방에 혼자 남겨두고
passion will explode
그리고 열정은 폭발할 것이다
whenever.
언제든지.
Why do I feel like this won't work?
왜 이것이 작동하지 않을 것 같은 느낌이 들까요?
Now we don't have to worry about that.
이제 우리는 그것에 대해 걱정할 수 없습니다.
When you say "three, two, one," turn off the power.
"셋, 둘, 하나"라고 말하면 전원을 꺼주세요.
OK?
좋아요?
OK
좋아요.
[Contents of work manual]
[작업 매뉴얼 내용]
This is very nice.
아주 좋다.
You have worked hard.
당신은 열심히 일했습니다.
I didn’t do much work. This is what I have to do.
나는 일을 많이 하지 않았습니다. 그것이 내가 해야 할 일이다.
Did you spend a lot of time doing this?
이 작업을 수행하는 데 많은 시간을 보냈습니까?
a few nights.
여러 밤.
Is anyone here?
거기 누구 없나요?
There are people inside.
안에는 아직 사람들이 있습니다.
The power is gone.
전기가 나갔습니다.
Is anyone here? There are people inside.
거기 누구 없나요? 안에는 아직 사람들이 있습니다.
[Fang Mingfan]
[팡밍판]
(Boss, she’s leaving.)
(사장님, 그 사람 곧 떠날 거예요.)
(If you don't say what you want to say, your time will run out.)
(하고 싶은 말을 하지 않으면 시간이 부족해집니다.)
Is anyone here?
거기 누구 없나요?
(I can only help you so far.)
(지금까지만 도와드릴 수 있습니다.)
(Good luck.)
(행운을 빌어요.)
Is anyone here?
거기 누구 없나요?
Fang Mingfan
팡밍판
He turned off the power on purpose.
그는 일부러 전원을 껐다.
My flight is this afternoon.
내 비행기는 오늘 오후야.
I have already coordinated with Jiang
나는 이미 Jiang과 조율을 했습니다.
about work.
직업에 대해.
If Jiang made a mistake,
장쩌민이 실수하면
Please understand and encourage her.
그녀를 이해하고 격려해주세요.
I lied.
나는 거짓말을 했습니다.
What is my boss saying?
우리 상사가 뭐라고 하는 거야?
I want you to stay,
나는 당신이 머물기를 원합니다.
Not because we need a translator,
번역가가 필요해서가 아니라
Not even because you know French and medicine.
당신이 프랑스어와 의학을 알고 있기 때문도 아닙니다.
When I first met you in Lakaya
라카야에서 처음 만났을 때 ,
I thought you were a person who only pursues your own interests.
자기 이익만 추구하는 사람인줄 알았는데
medical deserter
의료 탈영병.
but
하지만
When you talk about medical terminology, you are familiar with it.
의학용어에 관해 이야기할 때, 당신은 매우 친숙했습니다.
you can do anything
너는 무엇이든 할 수있어
To save Saquon.
사쿤을 구하기 위해.
Even you are in the way
심지어 방해도 했어
Between me and the stick, between me and the gun.
나와 막대기 사이, 나와 총 사이.
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
Do you remember that night at the pharmacy?
그날 밤 약국에서 있었던 일을 기억하시나요?
It was as dark as it was now.
지금처럼 어두웠습니다.
You help me arrange the letters on the bracelet.
당신은 내 팔찌의 글자를 정리하는 데 도움을 주었습니다.
You look really beautiful
정말 아름다워 보이셨어요
Under the jacaranda tree
자카란다 나무 아래
When you take off your makeup.
화장을 지웠을 때.
Doctor Gu.
구 박사님.
Don't be too sentimental.
자만하지 마라.
I did the things you said without thinking.
말씀하신 것들은 별 생각 없이 했는데요.
If I saw someone today in the situation you describe,
오늘 당신이 묘사한 것과 같은 상황에 처한 사람을 본다면 ,
I would do the same thing, I would put myself between them and the danger.
나도 똑같이 할 것이고 그들과 위험 사이에 나 자신을 놓을 것입니다.
Wei'an.
웨이안.
That New Year's kiss
그 새해의 키스
It wasn't just a kiss.
그것은 단순한 키스가 아니었습니다.
I don't want to be just your friend.
나는 단지 당신의 친구가되고 싶지 않습니다.
Basta.
바스타야.
I know what you're going to say.
나는 당신이 무슨 말을 하려는지 알아요.
Since the New Year's dance,
새해부터 댄스,
I already know.
나는 이미 그것을 알고 있었다.
I'm not stupid.
나는 바보가 아니다.
I can see it in your eyes
나는 당신의 눈에서 그것을 볼 수 있습니다
And hear it in your words.
그리고 당신의 말을 들어보세요.
But I'm glad you didn't say it.
하지만 당신이 그런 말을 하지 않아서 다행이에요.
so
그래서
I can continue to act stupid.
계속 바보처럼 놀 수 있어요.
I have no patience for anything
나는 모든 일에 참을성이 없고,
in medicine
의학에서
and in love.
그리고 사랑에 빠졌습니다.
So, no matter what impression I gave you before,
그러니까 아까 제가 여러분에게 준 인상과는 상관없이,
Now I like Eliot,
이제 나는 엘리엇을 좋아한다.
I will go to Paris with him.
그리고 나는 그와 함께 파리로 갈 것이다.
you understand?
이해하셨나요?
Do you like Eliot?
엘리엇을 좋아하시나요?
Oh, really?
오, 진짜?
It's not good to force things.
억지로 하는 것은 좋지 않습니다.
For someone like me, it's not worth it.
나 같은 사람에게는 그럴 가치가 없습니다.
Stop wasting your time on me.
나한테 더 이상 시간을 낭비하지 마세요.
Jiang, open the door.
장, 문 좀 열어봐.
I know you're out there.
당신이 밖에 있다는 걸 알아요.
Jiang.
장.
Are you asleep?
잠들었 니?
The recorder is smart.
녹음기는 똑똑해요.
I tagged common terms used in neurosurgery
신경외과에서 자주 사용하는 용어를 라벨로 붙였습니다
in the dictionary.
사전에.
And that cream
그리고 그 크림
It's to relieve itching,
가려움증 때문이에요
People who have used it say it works very well.
써본 사람들은 효과가 아주 좋다고 하더군요.
Jiang.
장.
Fang Mingfan is very kind to you.
Fang Mingfan은 당신을 매우 잘 대합니다.
You should appreciate it.
당신은 그것을 감사해야합니다.
(River.)
(장.)
(sorry.)
(죄송합니다.)
(There's something I don't know how to tell you.)
(어떻게 말해야 할지 모르겠습니다.)
(I have to find a cure)
(치료법을 찾아야 해요)
(Before my condition worsened.)
(병이 진행되기 전에.)
(I have to go to France.)
(나는 프랑스에 가야 해요.)
【Friendship Hospital】
[우정병원]
Hilo.
안녕하세요.
Hemostatic gel.
지혈 젤.
The bleeding has stopped.
출혈은 이미 멈췄습니다.
Fang Mingfan.
팡밍판.
Close up of skull.
두개골을 닫습니다.
OK
좋아요.
boss.
사장.
This is the last surgery of the day.
오늘이 마지막 수술입니다.
I'll take care of the rest.
나머지는 제가 처리하겠습니다.
You can go first.
먼저 가셔도 됩니다.
Where should I go?
난 어디로 가야 해?
Wei An is probably already on his way to the airport.
웨이안은 이미 공항으로 가는 중일 것이다 .
Wei An, are you feeling uncomfortable?
웨이안 씨, 불편해요?
We are about to arrive at the airport.
우리는 곧 공항에 도착할 예정입니다.
No, I'm thinking
아니, 내 생각엔
Significant changes in mice
쥐의 눈에 띄는 변화
People who have received cell transplants ,
세포 이식을 받은 사람 ,
As the material you showed me shows .
당신이 보여줬던 자료에 나온 대로요 .
Dr. Marta should be ready
마르타 박사님은 준비가 되어 있어야 합니다
Move your research into clinical trials, right?
당신의 연구를 임상 실험으로 가져가는 거죠 , 그렇죠?
perhaps.
아마.
what happened?
무슨 일이야?
Is there any progress in research?
연구에 진전이 있었나
oh
영형
Are they stagnant?
정체되어 있나요?
In fact, in Paris, there are many top laboratories.
사실 파리에는 최고 수준의 연구실이 많이 있어요.
Dr. Marta is also studying
마르타 박사도 연구 중
Brain-computer interface has huge potential.
엄청난 잠재력을 지닌 두뇌-기계 인터페이스입니다 .
If you are interested, I can help you coordinate.
관심이 있으시면 조정을 도와드릴 수 있습니다.
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
you know.
알잖아.
I just want to join the Huntington's Disease Project.
저는 헌팅턴병 프로젝트에 참여하고 싶습니다 .
Project Progress
프로젝트 진행
Huntington's disease develops very slowly.
헌팅턴병의 진행 속도는 매우 느립니다.
You can join other research groups
다른 연구 그룹 에 참여할 수 있습니다.
While you wait for the Huntington's Disease Project
헌팅턴병 프로젝트를 기다리는 동안
Entering the clinical stage,
임상 단계로 나아가고,
Then you join their team.
그리고 당신은 그들의 팀에 합류합니다.
No.
아니요.
I can't wait any longer.
나는 잠시 더 기다릴 수 없다.
Because you can't wait?
기다릴 수 없기 때문에?
Why only Huntington’s disease?
왜 헌팅턴병만 있는 걸까요?
Why are you following me?
왜 나를 따라오나요?
This is what Wei An left for you.
이것이 Wei'an이 당신에게 남긴 것입니다.
Immediately perform an enhanced CT scan of the head.
조영제를 사용하여 머리 CT 스캔을 즉시 수행하십시오 .
There is a mass in the brainstem.
뇌간에 덩어리가 있습니다.
Multimodal magnetic resonance imaging .
다중모달 자기공명영상 .
Consider the possibility of high-grade glioblastoma.
고등급 교모세포종의 가능성이 높다고 생각됩니다 .
There is a mass in the brainstem.
뇌간에 덩어리가 있습니다.
Multimodal magnetic resonance imaging .
다중모달 자기공명영상 .
Consider the possibility of high-grade glioblastoma.
고등급 교모세포종의 가능성이 높다고 생각됩니다 .
This is a smart voice recorder.
이것은 스마트 녹음기입니다.
When you say a keyword,
키워드를 말하면
Autoplay with corresponding French translation.
해당 프랑스어 번역을 자동으로 재생합니다 .
Wei An has compiled your most commonly used phrases
Wei'an은 당신이 가장 많이 사용하는 문구를 편집했습니다
According to your work manual,
작업 매뉴얼에 따르면,
And spent several nights recording them.
그리고 그것을 녹음하는 데 며칠 밤을 보냈습니다.
There may be traffic jams on the way to the airport now.
지금 공항으로 가는 길에 교통 정체가 있을 것 같습니다 .
I think you'd get there faster on a motorcycle.
오토바이를 타면 더 빨리 도착할 것 같아요 .
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
I mean,
내 말은,
If you don't leave soon, you won't find her.
빨리 떠나지 않으면 그녀에게 연락할 수 없을 것이다.
She said she must go to France with Elliot.
그녀는 엘리엇과 함께 프랑스로 가야 한다고 말했습니다.
Why should I go to her?
내가 왜 그녀를 찾으러 갈까요?
This is a question only you can answer .
그건 당신만이 대답할 수 있는 질문이다 .
Doctor Gu, do you know?
구 박사님, 알고 계셨나요?
Wei An once filled in a textbook
웨이안은 교과서를 채우곤 했어
And your name.
당신의 이름으로.
After I found out, he explained to me
내가 그걸 알고 나서 그는 나에게 설명을 해주었다.
She wants to be a doctor like you.
그 사람도 당신 같은 의사가 되고 싶어 했다고요.
But do you believe this?
그런데 당신은 그걸 믿나요?
I have never seen any doctor
나는 의사를 본 적이 없다.
Fill a book with the name of Hippocrates.
히포크라테스의 이름으로 책을 채우세요 .
Even if I...
비록 내가...
Doctor Gu.
구 박사님.
I don't know why Vian went to France;
웨이안이 왜 프랑스로 가는지는 모르겠지만,
But it certainly wasn't for Eliot.
하지만 엘리엇에게는 그렇지 않을 것 같아요.
♪Your secret♪
♪너 비밀♪
♪Luckily, I hear all your dreams♪
♪다행히도 너의 꿈은 다 들려♪
♪Come closer, I can feel the curve of your smile♪
♪가까이 와라 너의 미소의 곡선이 느껴져♪
♪This is an extension of happiness♪
♪행복의 연장입니다♪
♪ again and again ♪
♪몇번이고 또♪
Don't take a step closer to Dr. Gu.
구 박사님께는 한 발짝도 가까이 다가오지 마세요 .
Unless I die.
내가 죽지 않는 한.
♪I've been waiting for this moment for a long time♪
♪ 오랫동안 이 순간을 기다렸어요 ♪
♪I will dream about you again♪
♪다시 한번 당신의 꿈을 꾸게 될 것입니다♪
♪Your secret♪
♪너 비밀♪
♪Luckily, I hear all your dreams♪
♪다행히도 너의 꿈은 다 들려♪
♪Come closer, I can feel the curve of your smile♪
♪가까이 와라 너의 미소의 곡선이 느껴져♪
♪This is an extension of happiness♪
♪행복의 연장입니다♪
♪ again and again ♪
♪몇번이고 또♪
♪My secret♪
♪미 비밀♪
♪I have forgotten that I was once an island♪
♪내가 한때 외로운 섬이었다는 사실을 벌써 잊어버렸어요♪
♪I've been waiting for this moment for a long time♪
♪ 오랫동안 이 순간을 기다렸어요 ♪
♪I will dream about you again♪
♪다시 한번 당신의 꿈을 꾸게 될 것입니다♪
Wei'an.
웨이안.
Your interest in and knowledge of Huntington's disease is unusual.
헌팅턴병 에 대한 귀하의 관심과 지식은 정상적이지 않습니다.
patient
환자
Is he really your friend?
그 사람 정말 네 친구야?
[Gene test report] [Name: Su Weian]
[유전자 검사 보고서] [이름: Su Wei'an]
Amplification of cytosine, adenine and guanine
증폭된 시토신, 아데닌, 구아닌 의 양
greater than forty,
마흔보다 크고,
Carry the gene that causes Huntington's disease.
헌팅턴병의 병원성 유전자를 가지고 있습니다 .
Wei'an.
웨이안.
It's you.
당신이에요.
So you know why.
그래서 당신은 이유를 알고 있습니다.
This is the only reason I go to Paris.
그것이 내가 파리에 가는 유일한 이유이다 .
Sorry, Vianne.
미안해, 웨이안.
I can't take you to Paris.
나는 당신을 파리로 데려갈 수 없어요.
because?
왜냐하면?
Elliot.
엘리엇.
I just want to participate in Dr. Marta's experiment.
나는 단지 마르타 박사의 실험에 참여하고 싶었을 뿐입니다.
I will never bother you.
나는 확실히 당신을 귀찮게하지 않을 것입니다.
Don't have any burden in your heart.
마음에 무게를 두지 마십시오.
The experiment failed again.
실험은 또 실패했습니다.
This project has been cancelled, sorry.
이 프로젝트는 이미 취소되었습니다. 죄송합니다.
Cancel?
취소 된?
Sorry, Wei An, I lied to you.
미안해, 웨이안. 내가 거짓말을 했어.
Wait, but the progress of animal experiments
잠깐만요, 그런데 동물실험의 진전이
What I'm showing you is very successful.
제가 보여드린 것은 매우 성공적이었습니다.
Why was it cancelled?
왜 취소되었나요?
The video I showed you
제가 보여드린 영상
That was three months after taking the medication.
약을 먹은지 3개월이 지난 후였습니다 .
However, in fact, six months later,
그러나 실제로는 6개월 후,
Mouse mortality
생쥐의 사망률
More than sixty percent.
60%를 초과했습니다.
The experiment failed again.
실험이 또 실패했습니다.
Wei An, I'm sorry.
웨이안 씨, 미안해요.
I just want to take you to Paris.
난 그냥 당신을 파리로 데려가고 싶었어요.
I just feel that the air in Paris is full of love,
사랑이 가득한 파리의 공기가
It will create a beautiful chemical reaction between us .
우리가 함께 아름다운 화학반응을 하게 될 거에요.
But I never thought about it...
그런데 전혀 생각도 못했는데...
sorry.
죄송합니다.
no problem.
괜찮아요.
I should get used to being disappointed.
나는 실망에 익숙해져야 한다.
That's really part of the script, right?
이것은 실제로 대본의 일부입니다. 그렇죠?
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
Genetic test report
유전자 검사 보고서
It won't change anything.
아무것도 바뀌지 않습니다.
If you still want to go to Paris with me...
그래도 나랑 같이 파리에 가고 싶다면...
boarding pass.
탑승권.
Please show your boarding pass.
탑승권을 보여주세요.
Wei'an.
웨이안.
Excellent.
훌륭한.
I finally arrived on time.
드디어 정시에 도착했어요.
Wei'an.
웨이안.
do not go.
가지 마.
OK?
좋아요?
Wei An, are you okay?
괜찮아, 웨이안?
Where is Elliot?
엘리엇은 어디 있지?
he's gone.
그는 사라졌습니다.
he's gone?
그 사람이 갔나요?
Why did he leave you here alone?
그 사람은 왜 당신을 여기에 혼자 남겨두었나요?
what happened?
무슨 일이에요?
anything.
아무것.
Suddenly I don’t want to go to Paris anymore.
갑자기 파리에 더 이상 가고 싶지 않아요.
Don't you want to go to Paris?
파리에 가고 싶지 않니?
perfect,
완벽한,
I'll take you back.
내가 다시 데려다줄게
return?
반품?
Where else could I go?
또 어디로 갈 수 있나요?
Oye.
아야.
Yo…
에야디야…
I found your motorcycle.
네 오토바이를 찾았어.
I looked for her everywhere in Lakaya.
나는 라카야 전역에서 그녀를 찾았습니다.
When I found her,
내가 그녀를 찾았을 때,
I was completely devastated.
나는 완전히 파괴되었습니다.
I fixed it piece by piece.
하나하나 고쳐 나갔습니다.
you can fix
당신은 고칠 수 있습니다
Is something broken?
깨진 것 없나요?
if I could.
만약 내가 할 수 있다면.
I can fix anything that's broken.
깨진 것은 무엇이든 고칠 수 있어요.
Even to me?
나한테도?
That?
저것?
anything.
아무것.
Wei'an.
웨이안.
I returned it to its owner.
나는 그것을 주인에게 돌려줍니다.
from now on,
금후,
Don't lose it again.
다시는 잃지 마세요.
No.
아니요.
I have changed
나는 변했다
Most of the parts on this motorcycle.
이 오토바이의 대부분의 부품 .
so,
그래서,
It has become a common property between us .
그것은 이미 우리 사이의 공유 재산입니다 .
You can use it every day.
매일 사용할 수 있습니다.
But sometimes,
하지만 가끔은,
You can also carry
너도 가지고 다닐 수 있어
For busy leaders like me.
나처럼 바쁜 리더에게.
Thanks.
그라시아스.
Wei'an.
웨이안.
If you really want to go to France
정말 프랑스에 가고 싶다면,
We will have many opportunities in the future.
우리는 앞으로 많은 기회를 갖게 될 것입니다 .
We can make money here too.
우리 여기서도 돈 벌 수 있어요.
I'll help you do everything you want.
당신이 하고 싶은 모든 일을 도와드리겠습니다.
You dropped something.
당신이 뭔가를 떨어뜨렸어요.
Don't hold your child too tightly.
아이를 너무 꽉 붙잡지 마세요.
what happened?
무슨 일이야?
Wei'an.
웨이안.
I don't know what happened.
나는 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는지 모른다.
my son.
내 아들.
Has anyone seen my son?
내 아들 본 사람 있나요?
My son is missing.
내 아들이 사라졌습니다.
Do you have this doll?
이 인형이요?
is yours?
너의 것이 야?
human trafficking.
인신매매.
That?
저것?
Wei'an.
웨이안.
where are you going?
어디 가세요?
human trafficking.
인신매매.
Wei An just said that that person is a human trafficker.
방금 웨이안은 그 사람이 인신매매범이라고 말했습니다.
Come on, we have to call the police.
빨리, 경찰에 전화해야 해요.
There are traffickers in Friendship Hospital .
우정병원에는 인신매매범들이 있습니다 .
Please come and arrest them.
와서 그들을 체포해주세요.
oh!
¡오예!
Why did the police hang up on me?
경찰은 왜 내 전화를 끊었나요?
If the Lakaya police were effective
라카야 경찰이 효과적이었다면,
Human traffickers will not be so rampant.
인신매매범은 그렇게 만연하지 않을 것이다.
so...
그래서...
What are we doing now?
이제 우리는 무엇을 합니까?
hurry up.
더 빠르게.
Sit down.
잘 앉으세요.
Be careful.
조심하세요.
Give me the child.
나에게 아이를 줘.
Who are you?
누구세요?
You are crazy.
너는 미쳤어.
Want to die?
죽고 싶어?
dealer
딜러
Yes, I want to die.
네, 죽고 싶어요.
Give me the child.
나에게 아이를 줘.
You are too radical.
당신은 너무 공격적입니다.
Otherwise, they can harm the child.
그렇지 않으면 아이에게 상처를 줄 것입니다.
How many? I can buy kids.
얼마나 많이? 아이를 사줄 수 있어요.
Can you pay?
지불할 수 있나요?
how much money you have? Give me everything.
얼마나 많은 돈을 당신이 할? 나에게 모든 것을 제공.
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
I want to buy a child.
아이를 사고 싶어요.
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
Don't you have anything to do?
할 일이 없나요?
If we don’t buy the kids, someone else will.
우리가 아이를 사지 않으면 다른 사람이 아이를 사게 될 것입니다.
hurry up.
더 빠르게.
Ten thousand yuan in cash.
현금으로 10만 달러.
Very?
너무 많이?
I only have that.
나에겐 그것밖에 없어요.
rare.
아주 적습니다.
Alipay? Can I pay with Alipay?
알리페이? 알리페이로 ​​결제할 수 있나요?
are you kidding me?
나랑 농담하는 거야?
Get out of here now.
즉시 여기서 나가세요.
Wait a moment.
잠깐만요.
I'm really rich.
나 정말 돈이 있어.
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
The phone, and the money, all of that was a deposit.
전화, 그 돈, 이 모든 것이 보증금입니다.
You stay here. You go find the money.
당신은 여기있어. 당신은 가서 돈을 찾으십시오.
No, I want to stay here. He would go for the money.
아뇨. 저는 여기 남을 거예요. 그는 돈을 위해 갈 것입니다.
He is richer than me.
그 사람은 나보다 돈이 더 많아요.
what are you saying?
무슨 얘기를 하는 건가요?
Gu Yunzheng, I count to three.
구윤정 씨, 셋까지 셀게요.
Run quickly and don't look back.
빨리 달리고 뒤돌아보지 마세요.
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
Don't try to act like a diva.
여주인공처럼 행동하려고 하지 마세요.
We are here together.
우리는 여기에 함께 왔습니다.
We must go together.
우리는 함께 가야 해요.
Boss, what's wrong with this kid?
보스, 그 아이에게 무슨 문제가 있나요?
it's over.
끝났어.
This kid is all purple.
이 아이는 온몸이 보라색이에요.
He needs to be taken to hospital immediately.
그는 즉시 병원으로 이송되어야 합니다 .
It's all for you.
이 모든 것은 당신을 위한 것입니다.
Give me the baby, quickly.
빨리 아이를 주세요.
This time, we have to catch them.
이번에는 그들을 잡아야 합니다.
They come from the General.
그들은 장군 출신입니다.
have.
소유.
careful.
주의 깊은.
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
Don't move, everyone squat down.
움직이지 마세요. 모두 웅크려야 합니다.
Wei'an.
웨이안.
quickly.
빠른.
boss.
사장.
Fang Mingfan.
팡밍판.
You take your child to the hospital first.
당신이 먼저 가서 아이를 병원으로 데려가세요.
Go to the emergency room and get thoroughly checked out.
응급실에서 완전히 확인해보세요 .
OK
좋아요.
Jiang.
장.
My handbag.
내 핸드백.
My bag is on the motorcycle.
내 가방은 오토바이 위에 있어요.
Wei'an.
웨이안.
All my money is for my mom.
내가 가진 돈은 모두 어머니를 위한 것입니다.
My death insurance is finally available.
드디어 사망 보험을 사용할 수 있게 되었습니다.
¡ Wei'an!
¡ 웨이안!
assistance.
지원.
Wei An, desperate.
웨이안, 절망.
Doctor Gu, will Wei An...?
구 박사님, 웨이안은...?
Drive fast.
빨리 운전하세요.
hurry up!
서둘러요!
slowly.
느리게.
Wei An, stay strong.
힘내세요, 웨이안.
Doctor Gu.
구 박사님.
Is Translator Su injured?
번역가 Su가 다쳤나요?
half an hour ago,
한 시간 반 전,
There was a stab wound on the upper left side of the abdomen.
복부 왼쪽 상단 에 칼이 상처를 입었고 ,
It is estimated that he has lost more than 800 milliliters of blood.
그는 800밀리리터 이상의 혈액을 흘린 것으로 추정된다 .
No damage to visible organs was seen.
눈에 보이는 장기에는 손상이 관찰되지 않습니다 .
Does she have family here?
여기에 가족이 있나요?
Who signed?
누가 서명합니까?
I signed.
나는 그것에 서명합니다.
Let's take our time.
천천히 가자.
careful.
주의 깊은.
little by little.
조금씩 조금씩.
Okay, let's get started.
자, 시작해 보겠습니다.
We will take care of her.
우리가 그녀를 돌볼게요.
careful.
주의 깊은.
Dr. Xu.
슈 박사님.
The patient was in hypovolemic shock due to blood loss.
환자는 혈액 손실로 인해 저혈량성 쇼크 상태에 있습니다.
Be sure to check the abdominal cavity.
복강을 확인하십시오.
OK, I understand.
알았어, 이해해.
Moreover, his wound was close to his spleen.
게다가 그의 상처는 비장 근처에 있습니다.
Check carefully for internal damage.
내부 손상이 있는지 주의 깊게 확인하세요 .
return...
또한...
Doctor Gu.
구 박사님.
I am also a professional surgeon.
나는 또한 전문 외과 의사입니다.
You can entrust me with Su Translation.
저를 번역가 Su에게 맡기시면 됩니다.
Go get some rest.
가서 좀 쉬세요.
I am fine.
잘 지내요.
I'll wait here.
난 여기서 기다리고 있을게요.
Doctor Gu, you can't help.
구 박사님, 여기서는 도울 수 없습니다.
give it to me.
나에게 맡겨.
Please ask Dr. Xu.
쉬 박사님, 부탁드립니다.
Dr. Xu.
슈 박사님.
You must save Wei An.
웨이안을 구해야 합니다.
Hello?
¿ 안녕하세요?
boss.
사장.
I did a CT scan of that child's head.
나는 그 아이의 머리에 대해 CT 스캔을 했습니다 .
Brain injury has been ruled out.
뇌 손상은 배제되었습니다.
I have confirmed with the mother of the child
아이 엄마한테 확인했어요
People with no pre-existing medical conditions.
이전 병력이 없는 사람.
The emergency doctor has done a thorough examination.
응급 의사들은 이미 완전한 검사를 마쳤습니다.
He is currently out of danger.
그는 이제 위험에서 벗어났습니다.
By the way, where is Translator Su?
그런데 수 번역가는 어디에 있나요?
how is she?
그녀는 어때요?
He had just entered the operating room.
그는 방금 수술실에 들어갔다.
I will notify you as soon as there is any news.
소식이 나오는 대로 알려드리겠습니다.
My death insurance is finally available.
드디어 사망 보험을 사용할 수 있게 되었습니다.
Doctor Gu, what are you doing?
구 박사님, 뭐 하시는 거예요?
[Moutai liqueur, purchase price 42,710 francs. Priced at $100. ]
[마오타이 리큐어, 구입가 42,710 프랑. 판매가 100달러.]
【The first million investment plan】
[100만 투자 계획]
Doctor Gu.
구 박사님.
【Accidental Death Insurance】
[상해보험]
[Personal Accident Insurance] [Car Owner: Su Weian]
[개인 상해 보험] [소유자: Su Wei'an]
[Electronic Policy]
[전자보험 약관]
Is this death insurance?
이게 사망보험인가요?
What did Wilson Su mention?
Su Wei'an은 무엇을 언급했습니까?
Doctor Gu, what are you doing?
구 박사님, 뭐 하시는 거예요?
Wei An is not dead yet.
웨이안은 아직 죽지 않았습니다.
[Euthanasia]
[안락사]
[Euthanasia: Why not? ]
[안락사: 왜 안되죠?]
Also, Professor Gu, I would like to follow your advice.
그리고 구교수님 의 좋은 조언을 따르고 싶습니다 .
I can live without luster until I'm sixty.
나는 예순이 될 때까지 빛 없이도 살아갈 수 있었다.
Your life is worth more than mine.
당신의 생명은 나보다 더 가치가 있습니다.
If you live, you can save more people.
살아남으면 더 많은 사람을 구할 수 있다.
If he died, I would be responsible for my own life.
만일 그가 죽었더라면 나는 내 인생을 책임졌을 것이다.
Don't take a step closer to Dr. Gu.
구 박사님께는 한 발짝도 가까이 다가오지 마세요 .
Unless I die.
내가 죽지 않는 한.
Yes, I want to die.
네, 죽고 싶어요.
Give me the child.
나에게 아이를 줘.
(Su Weian, why do you always want to die?)
(소웨이안 씨, 왜 항상 죽고 싶어 하시나요?)
Does Wei An have any?
웨이안은 그랬나요?
Have you had any illnesses before?
전에 질병이 있었나요?
no way.
절대.
Where is his family?
그리고 그의 가족은요?
Are there any hereditary diseases?
유전병이 있나요?
In your family?
당신 가족 중에요?
No.
아니요.
♪Move the hands of the clock at night♪
♪밤은 시계바늘을 움직인다♪
♪The noise gradually replaced the silence♪
♪소음이 점차 침묵을 대체합니다♪
♪Our representative meeting script♪
♪회의 대본을 표현합니다♪
♪Embedded night rainbow♪
♪밤의 무지개를 담아♪
♪And the wind that passes through the desert♪
♪그리고 사막을 건너는 바람♪
♪Everyone is a witness to our past♪
♪모두가 과거의 증인이었어♪
♪No one can escape being lost in the vast world♪
♪ 광활한 세계에서 길을 잃을 수밖에 없는 사람은 없습니다 ♪
♪Looking for the one in a million possibility♪
♪ 백만 가지 가능성 중 하나를 찾고 있습니다 ♪
♪Trapped in this city called destiny♪
♪운명이라는 도시에 갇혀♪
♪But still chasing stars♪
♪하지만 여전히 별을 쫓고 있어요♪
♪Don't worry, I love those who are lost♪
♪걱정하지 마세요. 나는 길을 잃은 사람들을 사랑합니다♪
♪Holding a cup to warm the lonely soul♪
♪컵을 들고 외로운 영혼을 따뜻하게 ♪
♪Let me hug your crack♪
♪당신의 균열을 안아줄 수 있게 해주세요♪
♪You shine like a shining star♪
♪당신은 빛나는 별처럼 빛나네요♪
♪Blink in lonely moments♪
♪외로운 순간에 눈을 깜박인다♪
♪Move the hands of the clock at night♪
♪밤은 시계바늘을 움직인다♪
♪The noise gradually replaced the silence♪
♪소음이 점차 침묵을 대체합니다♪
♪Our representative meeting script♪
♪회의 대본을 표현합니다♪
♪Embedded night rainbow♪
♪밤의 무지개를 담아♪
♪And the wind that passes through the desert♪
♪그리고 사막을 건너는 바람♪
♪Everyone is a witness to our past♪
♪모두가 과거의 증인이었어♪
♪No one can escape being lost in the vast world♪
♪ 광활한 세계에서 길을 잃을 수밖에 없는 사람은 없습니다 ♪
♪Looking for the one in a million possibility♪
♪ 백만 가지 가능성 중 하나를 찾고 있습니다 ♪
♪Trapped in this city called destiny♪
♪운명이라는 도시에 갇혀♪
♪But still chasing stars♪
♪하지만 여전히 별을 쫓고 있어요♪
♪Don't worry, I love those who are lost♪
♪걱정하지 마세요. 나는 길을 잃은 사람들을 사랑합니다♪
♪Holding a cup to warm the lonely soul♪
♪컵을 들고 외로운 영혼을 따뜻하게 ♪
♪Let me hug your crack♪
♪당신의 균열을 안아줄 수 있게 해주세요♪
♪You shine like a shining star♪
♪당신은 빛나는 별처럼 빛나네요♪
♪Blink in lonely moments♪
♪외로운 순간에 눈을 깜박인다♪